[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M1_CutlassKeys",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Patricia",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M1",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M1_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M1_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M1_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M2_CursedDoubloons",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M2_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Grimm",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M2",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M2_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M2_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M2_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M2_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M2_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M2_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M3_MedusaRaidVector",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Trahern",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M3_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M3_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M3_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M3_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M3_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M3_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M4_MedusaRaid",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Trahern",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M4",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_M3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M4_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 2000,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M4_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@1039_RAID_Eggs_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@1039_RAID_Eggs_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@1039_RAID_Eggs_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@1039_RAID_Eggs_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q1_Build",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Arnold",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q1",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q1_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q1_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q1_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q2_FreePirates",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q2_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Bronn",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q2",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q2_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q2_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q2_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q2_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q2_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q2_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q3_Revelation",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 67,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Billiam",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q3_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q3_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q3_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q3_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q3_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q3_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q4_SpectralArtifacts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Kasper",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q4",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q4_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q4_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q4_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q4_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q4_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q4_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q5_Souls",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Rosina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q5",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q5_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q5_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q5_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q5_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q5_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q5_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q6_Citadel",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Decima",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q6",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q6_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q6_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q6_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q6_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q6_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q1R_Build",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Arnold",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q1R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q1",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q1R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q1_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q1R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q1R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q1R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q1R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Arnold_01",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q2R_FreePirates",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q2_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Bronn",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q2R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q2",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q2R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q2_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q2R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q2R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q2R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q2R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Q2R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q3R_Revelation",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 67,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Billiam",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q3R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q3R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q3_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q3R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q3R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q3R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q3_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Billiam_03",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q4R_SpectralArtifacts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Kasper",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q4R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q4",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q4R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q4_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q4R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q4R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q4R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q4R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Q4R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q5R_Souls",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Rosina",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q5R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q5",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q5R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q5_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q5R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q5R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q5R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q5R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Rosina_02",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_Q6R_Citadel",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_Q6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Decima",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_Q6R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_Q6",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_Q6R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 45,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_Q6_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_Q6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_Q6R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_Q6R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_Q6R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_Q6R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Decima_03",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S1_SeadogBrew",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Plute",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S1",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S1_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S1_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S1_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S1_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S1_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S1_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S2_AncientWonders",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S2_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Shillie",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S2",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S2_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S2_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S2_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S2_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S2_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S2_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S2_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S3_AeternumTriangle",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Shillie",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S3",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S2",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S3_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S3_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S3_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S3_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S3_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S3_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S4_ExplosiveProspecting",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Antonia",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S4",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S4_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S4_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S4_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S4_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S4_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S4_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S5_LightningBottle",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Fei",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S5",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S5_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S5_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S5_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S5_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S5_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S5_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S6_LightningBottleTest",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Fei",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S6",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S5",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S6_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S6_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S6_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S6_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S6_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S7_AnimalInstincts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S7",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S7_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S7_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S7_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S7_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S7_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S7_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S8_SnaggleTooth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S8_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S8",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S8_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S8_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S8_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S8_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S8_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S8_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S8_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S9_Catnipping",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S9_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S9",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S9_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S9_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S9_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S9_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S9_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S9_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S9_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S10_TamingTheLionhearted",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S10_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S10",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S10_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S10_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S10_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S10_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S10_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S10_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S10_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S11_PerfectCompanion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S11_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S11",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S11_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S11_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S11_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S11_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S11_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S11_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S11_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S12_DisturbingSilence",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S12_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Nekumanesh",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S12",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S12_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S12_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S12_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S12_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S12_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S12_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S12_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S13_TrackingByTeeth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S13_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Nekumanesh",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S12",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S13_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S13_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S13_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S13_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S13_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S13_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S13_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S14_HeartOfTheMarsh",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S14_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Nekumanesh",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S14",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S13",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S14_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S14_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S14_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S14_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S14_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S14_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S14_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S15_TreasureIsland",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S15_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Claire",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S15",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S15_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_S15_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S15_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S15_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S15_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S15_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S15_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M5_AdmiralBlackPowder",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Wally",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M5",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M5_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M5_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M5_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M5_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M5_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M5_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M6_MysteriesOfDeep",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Rowan",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M6",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M6_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M6_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M6_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M6_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M6_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M7_CleansingTreasure",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Quiggley_2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M7",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M7_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"Title": "@C10A_M7_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M7_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M7_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M7_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M7_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 1,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_M7R_CleansingTreasure",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 70,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_M7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Quiggley_2",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_M7R",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_M7R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_M7_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_M7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_M7_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_M7_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_M7_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_M7_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 1,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_M7_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S1R_SeadogBrew",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S1_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Plute",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S1R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S1",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S1R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S1_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S1_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S1R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S1R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S1R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S1R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_S1R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S3R_AeternumTriangle",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S3_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Shillie",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S3R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S3",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S3R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S3_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S3_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S3R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S3R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S3R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S3R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Shillie_05",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S4R_ExplosiveProspecting",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S4_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Antonia",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S4R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S4",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S4R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S4_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S4_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S4R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S4R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S4R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S4R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Antonia_04",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S5R_LightningBottle",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S5_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Table_LightningBottle",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S5R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S5",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S5R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S5_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S5_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S5R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S5R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S5R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S5R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Table_LightningBottle_02",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S6R_LightningBottleTest",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S6_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Fei",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S6R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S6",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S6R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S6_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S6_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S6R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S6R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S6_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S6R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Fei_05",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S7R_AnimalInstincts",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S7_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Table_AnimalInstincts",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S7R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S7",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S7R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S7_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S7_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S7R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S7R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S7R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S7R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Table_LightningBottle_02",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S8R_SnaggleTooth",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S8_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Table_Snaggletooth",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S8R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S8",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S8R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S8_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S8_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S8R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S8R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S8R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S8R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_S8R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S9R_Catnipping",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S9_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Table_Catnipping",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S9R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S9",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S9R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S9_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S9_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S9R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S9R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S9R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S9R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Table_LightningBottle_02",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S10R_TamingTheLionhearted",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S10_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Table_Lionhearted",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S10R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S10",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S10R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S10_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S10_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S10R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S10R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S10R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S10R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_S10R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S11R_PerfectCompanion",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S11_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Tosch",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S11R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S11",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S11R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S11_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S11_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S11R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S11R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S11R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S11R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_S11R_Cooldown",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "C10A_S15R_TreasureIsland",
		"Type": "Journey",
		"DifficultyLevel": 65,
		"FlagPvp": false,
		"CanBeShared": false,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "C10A_S15_Container_Main",
		"NpcDestinationId": "C10A_Claire",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 0,
		"AchievementId": "C10A_S15R",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "C10A_S15",
		"RequiredLevel": 65,
		"SuccessGameEventId": "C10A_S15R_Success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CK_PVEResource_DoubloonToken",
		"ItemRewardQty": 35,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 0,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": true,
		"Title": "@C10A_S15_Title",
		"Description": "@C10A_S15_Description",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@C10A_S15R_Prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@C10A_S15R_Proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@C10A_S15R_Incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@C10A_S15R_Complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ScheduleId": "Daily",
		"ObjectiveOnCooldownResponse": "@C10A_Claire_02",
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Marauder_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Marauder_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Syndicate_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Syndicate_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Covenant_objective",
		"Type": "Mission",
		"DifficultyLevel": 0,
		"FlagPvp": true,
		"CanBeShared": true,
		"CanFastTravel": false,
		"Task": "FM_10_PVP_Control_Covenant_container",
		"ExclusiveTerritory": 10,
		"RequiredLevel": 0,
		"ItemRewardQty": 0,
		"ShouldResetOnFactionChange": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": true,
		"Repeatable": false,
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": 0,
		"ShouldResetInProgressQuestOnScheduleEnd": false
	}
]